as a coach or course creator online
launching an offer is the number one
thing that you can do to make more money
in your business but most people don't
know how to do it the right way and they
don't know what the steps are so in this
video I'm going to break down for you
everything step by step of what to do to
launch your offer now for those of you
that I have not met yet my name is
Jeremiah Kowski and why should you
listen to me for the last 21 years I've
been in the coaching mentoring and
training space building some of the top
businesses over $10 million a year in
profit and I can help you get more
clients make more money and actually
have the kind of business that you want
that's not going to burn you out
something that you love something that
you get to enjoy and so today I want to
talk about creating and launching that
offer now we're not going to go into the
nitty-gritty of what software to use and
landing pages and all this that that
that's for other videos I want to talk
more about once you have your offer
ready to go how do you get it out there
to people so when it comes to having an
offer generally we Define it in two
stages number one you have something
that's paid that you're going to be
selling to people okay and you can price
this differently depending on who it's
for what the market is what the
intention on your funnel is the other
offer is having a free SL very low cost
offer so this one I might charge you
know $2,000 for this one might only be
seven bucks and what I'm going to do is
I'm going to promote this one right here
to build
trust with people
to buy this thing right here because the
fact is most people are not going to buy
something that's $2,000 simply because
it's awesome and there's enough coaches
and trainers out there that are selling
things that cost that much and more that
you need to have a strategy in place
that's going to build trust with people
okay and so to have that that's what
your your lead magnet is that's what
your landing pages and what we like to
promote is some kind of a lead magnet
that provides value to people it doesn't
over te it also doesn't oversell but it
shows people what it is and your your
system it's kind of like a a a checklist
of some sort you can actually have a
checklist be a lead magnet another thing
could be let's say a a video training of
some kind that goes over a topic this
video right here is an example the kind
of video that I'm even teaching right
here you could have on a page where
people have to sign up with their name
and email address to get a video to
listen to you train them okay okay
you're not providing transformation at
this level you provide transformation at
this level you hold back on the
transformation until people purchase
from you and this is key because I meet
a lot of coaches and mentors they want
to help so many people but the problem
is is that they are trying to bring
transformation to people that are not
making an investment and the problem is
you're actually doing people a
disservice because they haven't made an
investment they don't take the training
seriously and it actually discredits you
overall by doing that and so what you
want to do is you want to provide value
here but you're not giving all the
step-by-step how to everything is
accomplished in your free stuff does
that make sense the reason why is
because if you have a
business let me pause here there's a lot
of people they don't make money okay and
they provide a lot of great how-to
content and they're looking for
engagement but they're not making any
money and so if that's you and you don't
want to make any cash don't do this but
if you actually want to make cash flow
if you actually want to make six and
seven figures this is the process to be
able to do this and it's not that one
way is right or wrong they're just
different models if that makes sense so
a lot of people unfortunately are
following models of people that are not
even making any money when it comes to
building their business they're hoping
and praying that they get engagement the
algorithm shines its light upon them and
it pushes the content out to people
that's not a way to build a business
okay the way you want to build a
business is you want to be able to
communicate the value that you have to
offer you want to show people kind of
like a checklist that's in a verbal form
if it's on video or it could be written
or it could be in an ebook format and
then what you do is you promote that to
people right here so what I'm going to
go through is the process of actually
launching your lead magnet and actually
getting that out there to get people to
buy into your offer when you have your
offer right here a lot of people make
the mistake of just launching with this
and then they get disappointed when
nobody buys it and they feel like God
gosh I'm a failure and gosh nobody
purchased that thing that I spent so
much time and effort into and the truth
is it's just because that's not how the
world works it's kind of like expecting
somebody to marry you on the first date
or going up to your best friend and
saying hey will you marry me does that
make sense and it really is that way
it's not cheesy or silly to say it that
way because the problem is is that when
you're you have an offer that's for sale
that's a big commitment that you're
asking people for and so for you to
expect people to make that commitment
without knowing who you are without
being in a buying position without
feeling ready to purchase something
that's just simply not even realistic
and unfortunately that is the way that
most coaches and mentors think is that
if I have an incredible program with a
lot of value people are going to buy it
because it just rocks and it's so good
that people are just going to see how
amazing it is and they're going to
purchase it and that's just not the case
so you have to do is you have to go
through a process of building trust with
people over here before they ever
purchase something over here I've worked
with thousands of coaches and
unfortunately the ones who are
disappointed stressed out burnt out I
tried everything and nobody bought
anything they don't do this they just
put something out there and they get
disappointed when people don't buy the
thing that they're doing that they're
putting out there because they're not
actually taking the time to make a
connection with somebody they're not
taking the time to actually build a
connection to build trust so that then
that person can buy from them so that's
the number one thing that you want to do
is you actually want to create an offer
that builds trust with people once you
have that offer now it's time to launch
it and it's time to put it out there
generally you can come up with one of
these offers by figuring out okay what
is my paid system my paid system is
right here and I might have these
different pillars of ideas that I do I
know it looks kind of like a virus image
but it's not uh what this is is let's
say I help people grow their coaching
business but I might create an offer on
finding your Niche I might create an
offer on running ads I might create an
offer on creating a course does that
make sense so even though I help people
and in my coaching program the client
growth accelerator I walk you through
come alongside you and become a part of
your team to actually build your
business with you as part of this but
that's not
like everything that's in there there's
a lot of different factors to it so what
you want to do is you want to find one
piece of your system and create a lead
magnet around it so like I might create
a lead magnet around creating a course
that generate six figures I might create
a lead magnet around running Facebook
ads that get more clients I might create
a lead magnet around finding your Niche
all right and so based on that now I
want to build that out on a landing page
and I want to schedule a time when
people can actually register for that so
let's say my offer is a live event that
I'm going to be hosting okay so I got to
schedule the time for the live event and
this is the process that we go through
when we're launching an offer okay
number one we want
to schedule the time I think that's the
first thing find the date you want to
definitely name your offer you want to
figure out what the topic is about okay
and so that's going to be a a piece of
the thing that you're actually selling
you figure out a date and then you go in
and you you
build landing
page you write up
the autoresponder
emails
okay you
record
video
videos and like what kind of videos are
there well here here's the thing so when
you actually are creating your landing
page number one there something that I
recommend a lot of people do you want to
actually put a photo of you on the page
and on the thank you page you want to
have a video of you thanking them for
registering and have you with your face
directing them verbally speaking telling
them what actions to take so whenever we
launch an offer the first step is we
create that landing page we end up
writing up the autoresponders we create
what the thank you page is and then we
have some videos that are directing
people to go from stage one to stage two
to stage three in our autoresponder
emails I'm going to remind people for
what they registered for if it's a live
event I'm going to be reminding them
about the event any bonuses that we've
included you want to record any bonuses
if you have a part of that next what we
want to do is we want to
create promotional materials okay and
that's what we're going to be talking
about right now is that process of
actually creating the promo materials
when you're creating your promotional
materials you want to figure out who am
I trying to reach and what do I need to
say to get them to register for this so
what I like to do as part of our process
is I'll create a couple of Graphics in
Cana that have the title of what it is I
might even create a couple of of just
text Graphics that have some of the copy
from our landing page I'll create some
Instagram reels and we'll use those
Instagram res as advertisements both
organic and paid advertisements to get
people to register with us so that's
really the process of getting everything
ready to launch it is you want to put
get all of those pieces recorded you
want to get all those put together if
it's Evergreen you want to build out
whatever the Evergreen piece of content
is and now you have all of this ready to
go by the way I would not recommend you
take longer than about 14 days to get
this whole process done you know as
people we can really drag our feet
myself included to get offers out out
there to people and to launch them and
we can take a long time before we
actually put them out there dragging our
feet you know I I I look back on the
times where I've taken even 60 days to
create an offer because I was tossing
around in my head how I wanted it to be
how I wanted the funnel to be but the
truth is I was just analysis paralysis
overthinking the whole process if you
can pull yourself out of analysis par
is and you pull yourself out of worrying
what people think about you you become
willing to put yourself out there and
not worry am I doing it right or wrong
that's key and I tell you that one of
the biggest things that you want to do
is not worry throughout this process
because you will naturally have a
temptation to worry am I doing all the
right things is this going to work is
this going to come together the right
way
maybe you're concerned about how people
are going to judge you things like that
maybe you're concerned that it's not
going to produce the results that you
want ultimately this boils down to we're
trying to control things that are
outside of our control
by procrastinating with the things that
are inside of our control and that
becomes one of the biggest issues that I
find that people end up doing is there
are things inside of their control like
such as the landing page such as the
offer but they procrastinate through
doing those things because they're
delaying the inevitable of the things
that are outside of their control once
you put it out there it's outside of
your control but they're taking way too
long to actually get the stuff done that
are inside of their control so can I
tell you this that the reason why we
procrastinate is to avoid pain and we're
trying to numb out the Pain by doing
other things because we don't want to
experience potential Possible Pain or
disappointment and that's one of the
biggest reasons why that I noticed if
people don't launch their offer is
inside of their mind they are imagining
all the ways that it could go wrong and
they're letting those things prevent
them from actually doing the work to get
it done I work with hundreds of people
every single week I've coached thousands
of people over the years and I find that
this is the number one thing that
prevents people is our own thinking it's
our own
mind we come up with and ruminate and
and and process
all of the ways that things are not
going to be within our
control and yeah great let go of the
things you can't control control the
things you can but the problem is is
that we get caught in this Loop of
inaction where we are so concerned about
it not going how we want that we don't
do anything I find myself even
experiencing this on a daily basis when
I got to create content even videos like
this and so one of the biggest things
that you can do is to get yourself
in a mindset of action taking one of the
ways that you can do this that I find
that a lot of people don't do there's a
couple of things that I like to do
number one you could try to clean your
house it's actually a great thing to do
maybe you've been procrastinating a
certain room in your house getting that
done if you do that room in your house I
will tell you this you will feel
inspired to do the thing that you are
procrastinating on your business try it
out it's kind of crazy but it actually
works really well I find that if I'm
really putting off doing certain things
around the house that that actually is
one of the biggest reasons why I end up
procrastinating my business now that
sometimes it flips where I end up really
liking doing stuff in my house and now
that becomes the way that I
procrastinate so you want to be careful
with that you want to be careful that
you're not using these things that help
motivate you as a form of
procrastination and you start to really
pay attention to that and I think that
procrastination becomes a habit when
we're constantly used to putting things
aside that we need to do for the stuff
that we need to do let me explain that
again okay launching your offer is
something that you need to do in your
business but there's other stuff in your
life that you need to do and so what we
do is we literally numb out to not do
the stuff in our business that we need
to do to grow by doing the stuff that we
need to do outside of our business
pretty interesting and so what you want
to do is you want to make sure that you
don't don't allow that to get you caught
up in a cycle of productive
procrastination productive
procrastination and by the way you can
use this to your advantage is you want
to truly if we get at the core of it
it's about getting self-aware of why
we're doing what we're doing and not
letting those things become
ignored why am I avoiding creating my
landing page why am I avoiding recording
my ad
why even though I have all of this stuff
ready to go I know exactly what I want
to launch I know exactly what I want to
say am I avoiding putting it out there
and often times it's because we don't
want to be disappointed we don't want it
to not work out and we are allowing fear
and worry of things that might happen
outside of our control to take over our
own
actions but you're more powerful than
that you have the ability to do hard
things even if they don't feel good and
I'll tell you this as somebody who I
really believe that prioritizing peace
in your life is a great thing it's a
wonderful
thing sometimes there are moments when
you need to do the uncomfortable thing
when you need to do the thing that you
are putting off longer than anything
else and so once you get to that place
where you start creating a habit of
doing the stuff that you've been putting
off and taking it one step at a time
breaking it down into smaller chunks
taking it one step at a time figuring
out what's the thing that might help you
maybe put on some music that you like
heck put on a TV show on Netflix while
you're building your landing page now
don't get distracted just watching the
TV show again I've been guilty of that
but I I've also found that if I'm really
really struggling to gain breakthrough
in something I'll turn on a t T show
I'll turn on something to get my mind
off of the the the the
uncomfortability of the action that I'm
doing and kind of simultaneously watch
it in the background while I'm doing
that uncomfortable thing it's actually
something that I found that actually
works really
well let me tell you this not doing
anything is the wrong
choice figuring out how you operate best
to do something
that's what's going to help you more
than anything else and so now what are
those actions that you want to do once
you have all of those pieces that we
talked about on this
page ready to
go ready to put out there ready to
launch now it's time to actually launch
it so you want to take those Instagram
reels that you posted and what I would
do is once every day or so post one post
on all social media platforms where you
you're talking about something that's
related to the thing that you have in
your offer at the end of it you tell
people about the offer and where they
can find it one of the great ways that
we can do this now is you can tell
people to comment and use a tool like
many chat to be able to show them how to
do that you can use a tool like that to
to send them a link of where to register
you could tell them to go check a link
in your bio as well now that doesn't
always work if you want to run an
advertising campaign and that's how I
like to do it you also want to launch
these as advertisements we go into the
Facebook ads manager we we select the
audience that we want to
Target we figure out the psychology of
the people that we want to reach and
then we have the algorithm with a little
bit of money behind it push our offer
out there so that then people start
registering and so the goal is you want
to gather as many people in front of you
as possible and by the way that process
there's not much more to it than that is
it's really it's more built up in our
head that we have and if you can shrink
it down in your head how how big we have
it built up it becomes a lot simpler for
you so one of the things that I like to
do is to send out a couple of emails
couple of days before we launch the
offer tell people that something's
coming put some posts on social media
tell them that something's coming and
then we start posting these Instagram
reels and we start telling people about
the thing that we're going to be putting
out there we start seeding the idea
aidea of the result that they're going
to be getting out of it we start to get
people excited about the the result that
they're going to get from the free offer
that we have now you might be saying
well Jeremiah I thought you said at the
beginning of this to not deliver
transformation in the free offer can I
tell you this the transformation is
going to come by them going through the
free offer and then them purchasing the
thing on the back end of it so you want
to be very excited in your
communication in the promotion process
about the transformation that they're
going to get on the back end but the way
that they got to get there is by coming
in through the gate through the door of
your free offer if I want to go to the
rodeo I got to walk through the gate and
pay for a ticket and on my way there I'm
going to be presented with offers for
popcorn and beer and soda and and all
manner of memorabilia and stuff like
that right so you got to walk people
through that process and by the way in
in in all business that really is one of
the number one pieces of psychology that
you have to understand is in business
let's say that you have a store right
here and on the back shelf there is gold
okay this is your offer this is what
you're
selling but people have to come through
the front
door right there and so then they got to
go down the aisle and they got to turn
this way and turn this way before they
find the gold on the back shelf and so
the thing that you want to do your lead
magnet is like the parking lot that
you're directing them to you're telling
people where to find it where to come
you're telling them about the incredible
gold that you have now check this out
you're not going to give them the gold
just by showing up at the front
door you're not going to give them the
thing that they're buying into just by
showing up at the front door no they got
to go through the process and then they
got to bring it to the register to
purchase
it and yet so often as coaches and
mentors we're like well just come to the
front door and I'll give it to you here
you go here you go because we're looking
for so much
validation we're looking for people to
validate us instead of taking people
through the necessary
process to reach the outcome that
they're looking for in all business
there is a process in the buying
perspective in the purchasing
perspective and that process is
strategically designed did you know that
if you go to Target they strategically
put products in different parts of the
store because they know that you are
more likely to buy them if you have to
walk through a certain psychological
process of how the store is laid out in
physical
space there are billions of dollars
spent studying
this and there are billions of dollars
spent studying how to sell coaching
programs the same way as well and so
what your goal is is that when you're
launching an offer you're wanting to let
people know about the gold that you have
you want to let them know about how
amazing it is and you're directing them
to the parking lot into the front door
which is your free offer you're
directing them to get that incredible
outcome by coming to your free offer you
know I meet a lot of coaches and they're
like well I just I don't feel ethical
about not giving this incredible result
for free to
people and yet if they had a brick and
mortar store they wouldn't feel
unethical about Not Giving gold to
people just for coming to the parking
lot it's interesting and yet it's the
same thing it's the same exact
scenario and so we got to shift our
perspective and you have to start to see
your value more I think one of the
biggest reasons why we struggle to sell
in our business why we struggle to
launch our offers is we don't see our
own value and we don't respect it enough
and we don't have enough respect for the
value that we have inside of us to give
to people you have gold inside of you
and just any Yoo out there doesn't
deserve it
you want to give many are called to come
to find the gold but few are
qualified I know that's not what the
Bible says but that's what I'm saying
right here many are called with our
offer but few are qualified for it and
so people qualify themselves by actually
walking through the door and actually
going through the
process and then that's where you
deliver that exciting
result and transformation that you
promised on the back end of it and so
when you're launching an offer you want
to be excited you want to promise
incredible things from the
beginning as people go through that
process with you to invite them into a
journey with you to experience something
that's absolutely incredible that will
change their life you know when my
clients come into my accelerator program
they're looking to get more clients
because they're struggling to even get
people to show up in the parking lot let
alone buy something and when I can walk
them through a process to be able to
create 10,000 20,000 $30,000 a month by
showing them how to find their Niche how
to dial in their messaging how to get
their sales process in order and how to
structure all of this to put it together
and they actually start making money to
have time and Financial Freedom so that
they can have consistent income so that
they don't have sporadic income so they
have clear messaging and so they
actually start to have massive impact
that they crave if you want massive
impact this process that I've just shown
you here is how you do that and listen
I'd love to work with you in my
accelerator program to show you how to
get those results I'd love to work with
you inside of my program to walk you
through that process with me make sure
you subscribe to this channel get on the
waiting list for our accelerator program
and jump in next time we have a
training and I'd love to help you get
more results in your business that you
don't struggle and you can actually make
the kind of money that you want to make
as a coach or Mentor all right we'll see
you soon hey let let me know in the
comments if there's anything else you
love us to make a video on and we'll
talk soon have a good one